export const boatFishing = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: '1. Boat fishing allows you to reach hard-to-access spots.',
    answers: ['True', 'False'],
    correctAnswer: 'True',
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: '2. Boat fishing is always safe.',
    answers: ['True', 'False'],
    correctAnswer: 'False',
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question:
      '3. When boat fishing, it is important to consider the wind and current.',
    answers: ['True', 'False'],
    correctAnswer: 'True',
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: '4. Boat fishing requires special equipment.',
    answers: ['True', 'False'],
    correctAnswer: 'True',
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: '5. Boat fishing is only effective on lakes.',
    answers: ['True', 'False'],
    correctAnswer: 'False',
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question:
      '6. Boat fishing allows the use of both spinning and float tackle.',
    answers: ['True', 'False'],
    correctAnswer: 'True',
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question: '7. Boat fishing requires the mandatory use of a fish finder.',
    answers: ['True', 'False'],
    correctAnswer: 'False',
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: '8. Boat fishing does not require a life jacket.',
    answers: ['True', 'False'],
    correctAnswer: 'False',
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question: '9. Boat fishing allows you to fish at different depths.',
    answers: ['True', 'False'],
    correctAnswer: 'True',
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question: '10. Boat fishing is convenient for catching large fish.',
    answers: ['True', 'False'],
    correctAnswer: 'True',
  },
];
